BOBBIE WILSON

575-494-6644 • bobbiewilson75@yahoo.com

SUMMARY

Attentive, detail oriented RN with 10 years experience in Level I and II Trauma Center Emergency Departments. Highly effective communicator committed to consistently surpassing patient's expectations. Productive, hard working emergency department nurse looking to utilize my extensive bedside emergency nursing knowledge in a clinical documentation improvement setting.

SKILLS

10 years experience in Level I and II Trauma

Center Emergency Departments.

Direct, conscientious, effective communicator.

Detail oriented.

Consistently hard working, quick learner.

Experience with Epic, Cerner and Meditech EMR documentation.

Experience with Pyxis medication dispensing.

EXPERIENCE

Registered Nurse

Atlas Medstaff | Omaha, NE | Apr 2012-Current

Facilitate patient placement and manage nurse to patient ratio.

Effectively communicate with all healthcare members to ensure consistent, quality care.

Accurately and completely utilizing EMR to document patient's diagnosis, all treatments/medications administered, reassessment, and patient's response.

Assessment of patient and family knowledge and provide education based on knowledge deficit.

Assist physicians with various bedside procedures, including conscious sedation, orthopedic reductions, cardiac conversion.

Consistently and eagerly provide exceptional patient care while continuously motivating and encouraging patient's and families to adhere to prescribed plan of care during visit and after discharge.

Resuscitation and stabilization of various trauma patients.

Registered Nurse

Vidant Health | Greenville, NC | Jun 2012-Apr 2016

Facilitate patient placement and manage nurse to patient ratio.

Effectively communicate with all healthcare members to ensure consistent, quality care.

Accurately and completely utilizing EMR to document patient's diagnosis, all treatments/medications administered, reassessment, and patient's response.

Assessment of patient and family knowledge and provide education based on knowledge deficit.

Assist physicians with various bedside procedures, including conscious sedation, orthopedic reductions, cardiac conversion.

Consistently and eagerly provide exceptional patient care while continuously motivating and encouraging patient's and families to adhere to prescribed plan of care during visit and after discharge.

Resuscitation and stabilization of various trauma patients.

Registered Nurse

Sinai-Grace Hospital | Detroit, MI | Sep 2009-Jan 2012

Facilitate patient placement and manage nurse to patient ratio.

Effectively communicate with all healthcare members to ensure consistent, quality care.

Accurately and completely utilizing EMR to document patient's diagnosis, all treatments/medications administered, reassessment, and patient's response.

Assessment of patient and family knowledge and provide education based on knowledge deficit.

Assist physicians with various bedside procedures, including conscious sedation, orthopedic reductions, cardiac conversion.

Consistently and eagerly provide exceptional patient care while continuously motivating and encouraging patient's and families to adhere to prescribed plan of care during visit and after discharge.

Resuscitation and stabilization of various trauma patients.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Associate of Science: Nursing

Wayne County Community College District | Detroit, MI | 2009

CERTIFICATIONS

Advanced Cardiac Life Support, ACLS
Basic Life Support, BLS
Pediatric Advanced Life Support, PALS
Trauma Nursing Core Course, TNCC